# ABDUR REHMAN

**Associate Flutter Developer** 

LinkedIn: LinkedIn Profile GitHub: GitHub Profile

**PROFILE** 

A professional Flutter developer having 2 years of experiences in Mobile Apps development (Android & iOS). Focused on keeping a tight architecture in order to minimize errors and bugs. Successfully designed and built several mobile apps.

### **EXPERIENCE**

◆ Devex IT Enterprises (Pvt.) Ltd, Lahore || Flutter Mobile Apps Developer April, 2022 - Present

# **BOOTSTRAP ACADEMY**

. Udemy-type app where you can watch the courses which are in German language. This app was built for the famous German YouTube influencer *The Morpheus*.

Email: abdurrehmanlkl786@gmail.com

Mobile Whats-app: +923120998344

### **BRIGADE EXPERIENCE**

 Brigade Experience is a 2D-like game, where I build the front end of the whole app using Flutter. The technology used Google map, in-app purchasing, web sockets and Provider.

#### UNIT APP

- Unit app is a betting app which works on American betting odds. A lot of mathematics, Provider for state management with MVVM architecture and API implementation.
- ◆ Encoder Bytes (Pvt), Peshawar || Flutter Mobile Apps Developer May, 2021 - April, 2022

# PHARMAPEDIA PAKISTAN

comprehensive information mobile app builds in flutter & dart on medicines, drugs, brands, prices, and more, having 1 million downloads on the *Google play store*.

#### COIN BAZAR

A cryptocurrency app that is used for showing information about coins. Also create its admin in web Flutter. And hosted through Firebase hosting. (Firestore, Firebase).

# **EDUCATION**

♦ Islamia College University Peshawar || 2018 - 2022

BS Software Engineering, CGPA: 3.46/4.0

# **Skills & Technologies**

Front End Development: Java • Dart • Flutter

**Back Development:** NodeJS • Python

**Languages:** C++ • Java • JavaScript • Dart • Python • Flutter **Patterns / IDEs:** MVVM • Bloc • Android Studio • Vs Code

# **ACHIEVEMENT AND AWARDS**

# Got HEC Scholarship

Passed the most prestigious scholarship entry test of Higher Education Commission (HEC), who covered all my university (Bachelor) expenses.